
Warning: Module "pdo_mysql" is already loaded in Unknown on line 0

Warning: Module "mysqli" is already loaded in Unknown on line 0
Description:
  Assign the super admin role to a user

Usage:
  shield:super-admin [options]

Options:
      --user[=USER]      ID of user to be made super admin.
      --panel[=PANEL]    Panel ID to get the configuration from.
      --tenant[=TENANT]  Team/Tenant ID to assign role to user.
  -h, --help             Display help for the given command. When no command is given display help for the list command
      --silent           Do not output any message
  -q, --quiet            Only errors are displayed. All other output is suppressed
  -V, --version          Display this application version
      --ansi|--no-ansi   Force (or disable --no-ansi) ANSI output
  -n, --no-interaction   Do not ask any interactive question
      --env[=ENV]        The environment the command should run under
  -v|vv|vvv, --verbose   Increase the verbosity of messages: 1 for normal output, 2 for more verbose output and 3 for debug
